TAKE CHARGE OF MY HEART
Ms. Na.
I don't want to protect you anymore.
What?
I…
want you to be mine.
What's with this damn slow motion?
When's he going to kiss me?
Damn it.
Huh?
Is this what lips feel like?
What? I was dreaming about my own script?
Oh man.
Even in my dreams, I can't get anywhere.
Can't I at least get a kiss?
Shoot.
If I were the main character in a drama,
this is how I'd be introduced.
-Na Bo-bae, get ready now.
-Okay!
Name, Na Bo-bae.
A woman nearing 30
with an uncertain future ahead of her.
Ji-hye, where's that thing?
You know, my checkered hoodie?
Oh, that? I hung it outside.
My older sister, a soon-to-be-married
former national tae kwon do champion.
Hey, Yong-gi!
-Yeah?
-Yong-gi, give me that!
-This?
-Yeah.
Here.
My older brother, a former national judoka
who now runs his own dojo.
Then there's me,
the youngest and the only writer
in a family of athletes.
CONTEST AWARD
ONE-EP DRAMA (WISTFUL YOUTH)
I grew up surrounded by my family's love
despite being the odd one out, but…
I'm heading out!
-You're leaving?
-Yeah.
You're pushing 30.
How are you still always late for work?
Hey, Ji-hye. The bread.
I can't eat. My stomach hurts.
What do you mean? Just eat it on the way.
-My stomach hurts.
-Eat it.
-Just chew it.
-I'm off.
All right.
I left home after boldly declaring
I'd move back in with my parents
if I didn't make it as a drama writer
before turning 30.
Go crush it, Writer Na Bo-bae!
Now, I'm walking a tightrope,
on the verge of becoming a total failure.
Ugh, what's wrong with me?
Huh?
Oh…
Wow, he's exceptionally good-looking.
A guy like him would be perfect
for my male lead.
Oh, I meant I wanted him
as the male lead in my script,
not the male lead in my life.
Are you okay?
If this were a drama,
this would definitely be the start
of a romance.
But for me, this genre
is horror.
-Sorry! I'm getting off!
-That stings!
Because romance is a genre
that can never exist in my life.
Unlike in my scripts.
HYE-JU STRIDES AWAY
Ma'am!
(WITH A BURNING GAZE)
You got on the bus too?
(SHARPLY)
I told you not to escort me to work.
(AGITATED)
How could I not?
I'm going crazy worrying about you.
You're a bodyguard, so act like one.
You went too far.
(WITH A WARNING GLARE)
AS HYE-JU TURNS TO WALK AWAY,
I-HYEOK GRABS HER ARM
I-HYEOK PULLS HER INTO A ROUGH KISS
HYE-JU IS STARTLED AT FIRST,
BUT SOON MELTS INTO THE KISS
Did you put honey on your lips?
(BREATHLESSLY)
They taste so sweet.
Your lips taste even sweeter.
(POUTING)
Ms. Na, are you crazy?
What's wrong?
It was going so well.
Why fumble the kiss every time?
"Honey on your lips"?
What do we do with this?
What are they, bears?
Why would they taste like honey?
What kind of bodyguard kisses
their chaebol employer like that?
Isn't it bold and sexy?
It works in words, yeah.
But I'm at a total loss
for words, seriously!
Anyway, the male lead has only been
her bodyguard for two weeks.
Why is he suddenly head over heels
and grabbing her for a kiss?
Isn't that what happens
when you fall in love?
Like, you lose sight of everything else.
All you want is to be with this person.
You hear bells ringing, and--
Ms. Na.
Be honest with me.
You've never dated, have you?
My goodness.
I'm almost 30 now.
"Never dated"? Please. That's ridiculous.
Yeah? So you've dated someone?
Kisses, walks along the Hangang River,
theme park dates…
You've done all that?
Of course I've… done it all.
Are you kidding?
That's like the bare minimum.
Guys were lining up for me
back in the day.
Oh, really?
So what happened to your game?
Just look at your male lead.
The way you write it,
romance might as well be dead.
In fact, the coffin's nailed shut.
Of course it is.
I've never dated.
I'd run if a guy tried to hold my hand.
Honestly, everything else is fine.
When you debuted,
I couldn't stop praising you
and telling everyone I had dibs on you.
Great dialogue, great story.
The characters have depth.
So why do the characters always
go off the rails when romance hits?
Why must you let the viewers down?
Why stab them in the back? Why?
It's not like I do it on purpose.
Our contract ends in three months.
You do want to renew it, Ms. Na.
Don't you?
I do.
Three months.
I'll give you three months
to come up with a sexy romance.
Grab someone off the street
and date them if you have to.
A steamy, mature romance.
That's what I want.
Yes, sir.
TS RESORT, JEJU
Oh no! This is crazy. What do we do?
I can't breathe!
The rain got in my mouth!
Where are we going?
That way.
Please just pick up your phone! Come on!
Yes. Have you arrived?
You may head on up…
and ambush them.
TS RESORT, SEOUL
Who's going to brief him
on the Jeju resort?
It was the Jeju resort GM
who raised the issue. HR should handle it.
What are you talking about?
It's about booking cancellations.
That's the Rooms Division's job.
Jeez.
Man, just thinking about that young punk
smirking and nitpicking everything…
What's that?
Stomach medicine.
Oh, he's here.
Hello, sir.
Let's go.
Sir.
You're aware Jeju got hit pretty hard
by a typhoon recently, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
It seems the resort sustained
significant damage from the typhoon.
Thanks to your foresight, sir,
the buildings were built so well
that the facilities suffered no damage.
However, with the flight cancellations
and road damage,
I'm afraid we've had
many booking cancellations.
We are still assessing
the extent of the damage.
This, this, and that will be
our featured dishes this season.
Redo everything else.
We're still calculating
the exact value of the cancellations.
We'll update you by day's end.
Yes, so?
So, based on our analysis,
we may not meet the sales target
for TS Resort's 30th anniversary--
One of the lights is out.
Oh, I see.
We'll have it replaced right away.
We collected the cancellation fees,
so it isn't a total loss.
And the guests that are on-site
have decided to extend their stays,
so we'll collect additional charges.
You don't need to worry about that, sir.
-Is that so?
-Oh, yes.
Any difficult guests who refused to pay
were required to check out.
And who was it that made such a decision?
It was General Manager Heo Ji-hwan.
Right. General Manager Heo.
-Mr. Yoon.
-Yes, sir.
We changed the landscaping company, right?
Yes, sir.
Change it again.
They're all different shapes.
Yes, sir.
Director Jang?
Oh, yes, sir.
Could you call Mr. Heo?
Sure.
TS RESORT JEJU
GENERAL MANAGER HEO JI-HWAN
Mr. Heo?
Yes, sir. Have you been well?
The Jeju resort has been in an emergency
because of the typhoon,
and you've handled it very well.
Mr. Baek personally asked me
to give you a call.
Oh, it was nothing.
As the general manager of TS Resort Jeju,
I had to take firm action.
Please don't worry about the rest.
Hey, Ms. Go.
You ready?
Yes, we're in, sir.
What's going on?
Excuse me.
Look this way. Cheese!
What is this? Put that away!
Why the hell are you recording us?
-What's this about?
-Sir.
Just like you said, Mr. Heo
is having some kind of golf meeting
in the canceled suite.
Okay.
I just sent the video to Mr. Baek.
We've also secured photos of the scene.
-What?
-Mr. Heo, what the hell is this?
Where the hell did you guys come from?
You heard that, right?
Mr. Heo has been using canceled suites
for personal use, free of charge.
-Has he lost his mind?
-You didn't know?
You can't be serious.
Fire Mr. Heo immediately
and press charges.
Yes, sir.
Have the secretarial team apologize
to the guests
who were forced to check out.
I'll handle it right away.
And open up all the available rooms
at the Jeju resort
to the victims of the typhoon,
free of charge.
-Pardon?
-Sorry?
But that's…
Oh.
You said we might not hit our sales target
for our 30th anniversary, right?
I think
we can pull it off.
WISHING YOU A SWIFT RETURN TO NORMAL
No regular reservations.
We're only taking in
the victims of the typhoon.
You'll have to use the stairs.
Yes, the lobby is full.
Please direct them to the conference hall.
TS Resort Jeju has decided to open
the entire resort to typhoon victims,
free of charge.
Baek Ho-rang,
Senior Managing Director of TS Resort,
is converting the rooms and lobby
at TS Resort Jeju into emergency shelters
and plans to join the recovery efforts.
What about the Jeju resort?
Families with vulnerable members
were assigned to suites.
Private houses
were assigned by family or individual,
with individuals separated by gender.
And the support?
As requested,
all victims will stay free for a month.
We've sent supplies to the disaster area
and will be making a donation
through Jeju City Hall.
The media is praising TS Resort's
sense of social responsibility.
Public sentiment is positive,
and the stock is up.
Then it's time to find our new face.
Have you started looking?
The thing is…
Actor Ji Eun-ho is our first choice.
No. 1 in brand reputation and buzz
for months.
Dramas, movies, variety shows…
His idol-level popularity
means he's flooded with offers.
JI EUN-HO BRINGS AIRPORT TO A STANDSTILL
WHEN THE SCHOOL BELL RINGS
FOLLOWERS
JI EUN-HO
"WORLDWIDE FAME FEELS UNREAL"
JI EUN-HO EMERGES AS A GLOBAL STAR
He recently won Best Actor
at the Heuksang Arts Awards.
His drama was a massive hit,
so he has fans worldwide.
He's even received
an offer from Hollywood recently.
Not bad. So?
So, for the reasons I just mentioned…
we can't reach him, let alone sign him.
Mr. Yoon.
Are you kidding me?
Gosh, this is so stressful.
I've already got enough headaches
dealing with the Jeju resort
and figuring out a plan,
and now you?
I told you to sign him,
but you can't even reach him?
You call that a report?
Am I the only one working here?
Right now, I…
Sir.
You scared me.
I have a weak heart, you know.
Please calm down.
Take a deep breath.
Your heart rate is over 100 right now.
It goes over
whenever I try to do anything.
Deep breath.
Clear your mind
of distracting thoughts and worries.
Let go
of the urge to control
everything.
Where is Ji Eun-ho?
Pardon?
I'll sign him myself.
-Na… Bo-bae.
-Hey, Seo-jeong.
Looks like you got chewed out again.
What was it this time?
Romance? Physical affection?
-The kiss scene.
-Oh boy.
What does Director Yeom expect
from someone who's never dated?
Quiet. Someone might hear you.
Damn it.
It's doing it again.
What the… This isn't working either?
Damn it. What's going on?
Why isn't anything working?
I know. Nothing's working.
Nothing at all.
What?
-Bo-bae.
-No. I don't want to.
I don't wanna do it in public.
It's just us here. What's the big deal?
There are cameras.
-No, stop.
-Oh, come on. Please.
Director Yeom will lose it
if I don't hurry.
Help out your friend here. Please.
If you help me, I'll tell you
about this guy I met recently.
I'll tell you everything,
right down to the kiss.
Damn it.
Whoa.
Damn.
As expected of the human Pikachu.
I told you not to call me that.
I'm really sorry.
But thanks a lot, Bo-bae.
Love ya.
The truth is,
I have a secret
that I can never tell anyone.
-What should we eat?
-Well, I want sundae.
I want tteokbokki.
Then I'll have two bowls.
Then I'll have three bowls.
Then I'll have four bowls.
After lightning struck me,
I suddenly gained electrical powers.
Bo-bae.
When you're outside,
you must never touch anyone.
Electricity started to flow
through my body.
A cockroach!
-Ji-hye!
-What's wrong? What happened?
A cockroach!
Ji-hye, hurry up and catch it.
Ji-hye!
The more emotional I became,
the stronger my electrical powers grew.
Bo-bae.
You said you liked me.
You said you wanted to go out with me.
But you guys aren't even official yet.
I heard you even told him
not to hold your hand or touch you at all.
You even told her things like that?
Well, it's true.
You left me hanging
and wouldn't let me touch you.
Who would want to date you?
I ended up completely alone
thanks to this damn power of mine.
You can smile, right?
Whoa. Why are there so many people?
Hey, I think a celebrity's coming.
Put your gloves on.
I'm off.
I'll call you after work.
I've got a kiss story for you.
Thanks, you rascal.
Seriously, what's wrong with me?
Was my visit here leaked to the reporters?
I don't think so.
They aren't reporters.
Let's go.
Look, it's Eun-ho!
-I think it's over!
-Let's go!
Sir.
Hey.
Sir!
Sir.
Thank you.
Sir!
That was…
Well…
Are you okay?
Oh, yes.
As you just saw, I got pushed.
I know it was an accident.
Sorry about that.
Not at all.
Huh?
Sir!
Excuse me.
Wait! Hold on!
Wait.
Excuse me for a moment.
Nothing's flowing. For real.
What are you doing?
Earlier…
When our lips touched earlier,
did you feel anything?
Like a tingle? Or perhaps a spark?
No, I felt nothing at all.
If you'll excuse me…
Wait. Please excuse me.
What are you doing?
-Just a sec…
-What are you doing?
-Hold on.
-What's wrong with you?
-Please, just once.
-Hey.
-What's with you?
-Just once.
Just once.
Mr. Yoon!
Sir.
Still nothing.
Could this guy be immune
to my electricity?
Like a human rubber glove?
Excuse me.
What is it?
By any chance,
could we try just one more time…
Sir!
Are you all right?
Do you know her?
No, I don't know her.
I'm not interested in you, so please stop.
No, that's not it.
Can we talk for a second?
Just one moment. Can we please…
Wait. Can we talk for a second?
I'll be super quick.
-If you lay a finger on him…
-No, I…
I'm so sorry!
So why didn't anything happen to him?
What's wrong?
-What's wrong?
-My stomach…
Sorry!
My stomach hurts!
I'm sorry,
but I really need to see that man again.
My human rubber glove.
Does this hurt?
We'll get you to the hospital.
No!
Whoa, I wonder what happened.
The person they just took away.
Didn't she look like Bo-bae?
You mean, the writer?
Why would she be here?
Well, maybe she had a meeting here today.
Let me call her.
Eun-ho, you're making me nervous.
Today's meeting is really important, okay?
Yeah, I know.
If you disappear on me, I'm dead.
Call her after the meeting, okay?
-Damn it. This keeps falling.
-No answer.
-I have a bad feeling about this.
-Hey.
Hey, Ji Eun-ho!
Oh man.
Eun-ho, where are you going?
The director is waiting!
Did something happen to Eun-ho?
He's usually not like this.
Didn't you say you could get me a meeting
with Ji Eun-ho anytime I wanted?
He's nowhere in sight,
and I've been on a date with you
for the past 30 minutes.
You're right.
The time I'm spending with you
is just as precious and meaningful to me.
-Mr. Yoon.
-Ho-rang.
I mean, Mr. Baek! Please wait.
I'll do whatever it takes
to set up another meeting.
In return, could you put in a good word
for me at TS Resort?
They let us shoot there,
but half the place was off-limits.
Did your proposal include
any backup plans?
Backup plans?
Come up with an efficient shooting plan
and include Plans B and C.
They'll probably approve it.
Come on, Ho-rang. I'm your college senior.
Look, I'm on my knees.
If I still had to submit paperwork,
I wouldn't have asked you.
Meeting Ji Eun-ho
was my condition for helping you.
But Ji Eun-ho isn't here, is he?
Hey, Ho-rang.
That heartless bastard.
Plan?
Plan A, B, C, D, E, F, G!
Why not go all the way to Z?
You and your damn plans.
Pay up if you wanna film me,
you fucking bastards!
"TS Hotel's Choi Do-yoon."
"Drunk at club,
shouting, 'You f***ing bastards.'"
What a sight.
"TS Hotel's reputation
has taken a serious hit."
"The incident caused TS Hotel to drop out
of this year's major hotel rankings,
while its subsidiary, TS Resort, also fell
in the domestic hotel
and resort sales rankings."
I build up the company with the resort,
and he sinks it with the hotel.
What is this, a seesaw?
Find out where Ji Eun-ho is.
I need to see him in person.
You mean today?
Sir, you should head to the hospital
after this temple visit.
Our Plan A was for you to sign Ji Eun-ho,
but you failed.
Then Plan B.
We should've convinced Ji Eun-ho today.
But that fell through too.
Where do we go from here?
We go with Plan C.
Plan C is for me to go see him myself
if he doesn't show up.
It has to be today.
That's why my surgery's tomorrow.
-Still--
-And Plan D?
If we don't meet Ji Eun-ho today,
we'll postpone my surgery.
Yes, understood.
I'll find him no matter what.
Contact a suitable ad agency as well.
But first,
go say hello to your sister.
You're here.
Did you come to see your mom and dad?
Yes.
I thought they'd be happy to hear
this will be my last surgery.
BAEK GYEONG-SEOK
RYU MIN-SEON
You saw what Do-yoon did, right?
That brat is a lost cause.
After this surgery,
you'll be normal again, right?
I'm already normal as I am.
Make sure you come back healthy this time.
Any sign of weakness
will complicate the succession.
You need to become a leader like
your parents, flawless in the public eye.
Ma'am.
Ma'am!
Ms. Baek.
What is it?
Mr. Baek isn't in today.
Where did he go?
We can't disclose his schedule,
not even to his family.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me?
Does it look like I'm here
as Baek Ho-rang's family?
I'm here as the CEO of TS Hotel!
Isn't my name on his schedule today?
I'm sorry.
I don't want your apology!
My schedule.
Check, please!
-Mom, come on.
-Seriously.
You shouldn't yell
at such a beautiful young lady.
She startled you, didn't she? Sorry.
My mom's going through menopause
these days.
So?
Where's my one and only cousin?
Got it.
I'll call you right away.
Yes, understood.
Sir.
Ms. Baek and Director Choi Do-yoon
are at your office now.
Of all days,
they had to come see me today.
Typical of my aunt and cousin.
Anyway, did you say hello to your sister?
Yes. Thank you for being so considerate.
I finally got to see her again.
And I managed to find Mr. Ji Eun-ho.
He's at Taesung Hospital right now.
Taesung Hospital?
He's not sick.
It looks like he's visiting someone.
After we meet him…
we can see Professor Jang.
That's great.
Still nothing.
We've got the hottest star with us.
-Oh my, it's Ji Eun-ho.
-Please welcome Ji Eun-ho.
He looks just like my grandson.
Come on.
I bet the only thing they have in common
is that they're both human.
I'm serious, they really look alike.
Goodness. You always say that.
ACTOR JI EUN-HO
-Nice to meet you.
-Likewise.
WE FINALLY MEET HIM
I was wondering
when I'd see you in person.
I love your shows, Jaejae,
so I've been wanting to meet you.
-I'm truly honored to be here.
-Oh my.
As expected of the king of romance.
You've got a way with words.
WHAT A GUY!
SWEETNESS OVERLOAD!
So, Eun-ho,
you're known as the king of romance,
but you debuted in a youth drama.
Oh, yes.
Right. You made your debut
in the one-episode drama Wistful Youth.
And you said
it's still your favorite work.
That's right.
I binge-watched everything you've been in
when I heard you were coming on.
And wow, that one was a masterpiece.
I cried my eyes out for real.
Wow, thank you.
That project was where
my acting career truly began.
Ms. Writer, are you watching?
THIS ONE'S JUST FOR YOU
What's with him?
Bo-bae.
You don't hold back, do you?
You…
Eun-ho. Hey.
He's tall, like a model.
How did you know I was here?
I know everything about you.
All those all-nighters and takeout.
No wonder you ended up here.
That's not why I'm sick.
It's just that my appendix…
Your appendix? Did it burst?
Yeah.
Then don't you need surgery right away?
-I'll go get the doctor.
-Eun-ho, wait.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Ji Eun…
You're Ji Eun-ho, right?
There's a patient here named Na Bo-bae.
Oh, Na Bo-bae…
Yes.
Mr. Ji Eun-ho?
SENIOR MANAGING DIRECTOR
BAEK HO-RANG
So Director Yeom set up that meeting
for you to meet me?
Yes.
I asked him not to tell you.
I didn't want to put you on the spot.
Sorry I couldn't make it today.
A friend of mine suddenly got sick.
I should head back now.
Don't worry.
This hospital is part of TS Group.
If you tell me the patient's name,
I'll make sure they're well taken care of.
Have them moved to a VIP room.
In return,
I'd like you to make some time for me.
Mr. Baek Ho-rang.
Please direct all work-related matters
to my agency.
We're willing to accommodate
all your requests.
Well, you see--
Please send the patient's name
and date of birth
to the number on my business card.
You'll see what it's like
to work with TS.
Wow, he's so full of himself.
Oh man. Where'd that punk go?
-Punk!
-You scared me!
-Come with me.
-No, Hee-chan.
-Just five minutes.
-Five minutes?
-Are you sick?
-No.
Why are you in the hospital?
Bo-bae.
I'm sorry. Something urgent came up.
When's the surgery?
Oh man.
You and your Bo-bae. You're obsessed.
All right, then. I'll come by tomorrow.
Yeah. Get some rest.
Okay.
Come by where?
Your schedule's packed tomorrow, punk.
Why'd you suddenly take off?
You have no idea how much I had to grovel.
Hee-chan.
You knew I was meeting
Baek Ho-rang today, didn't you?
What? "Baekho"? Like a tiger?
What are you talking about?
I told you.
I don't mind promoting
my movies and dramas,
but I told you
I won't use my image for commercials.
-You said you'd keep them off my back.
-I did, but…
Turns out I couldn't do much.
Don't set up another meeting like that.
Find out who Ji Eun-ho visited earlier.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
You again!
I've been thinking about you
all this time.
-Did you come to see me?
-This is highly inappropriate.
So did you feel a tingle later?
I told you I didn't feel a thing.
Really?
-I knew it.
-Move aside.
Step aside!
Oh no, sorry.
I'm sorry!
Wait. Just a moment.
You see…
I know this is going to sound weird,
but you're the first person I've ever met
who's like a rubber glove.
Can we talk for a moment?
I have an appointment.
Then your number.
Can I at least have your number?
If you don't have time,
I'll explain everything in a text.
Please.
Could you just hear me out this once?
All right.
Then…
Your name?
I'm Na Bo-bae.
Ms. Na Bo-bae.
I've heard plenty of pickup lines,
but this kind of pathetic flirting?
That's a first.
"Flirting"?
One accidental kiss with a handsome guy
who looks loaded,
and suddenly it's "fate."
Don't you think it's a little cliché?
Even if I touch you, I don't feel a thing.
No tingle. No spark. No heat.
So please stop!
Gosh, what is he even saying?
Honestly.
Well done.
You couldn't even stop
a woman in a hospital gown?
The thing is, whenever we touched,
there was this static…
My apologies, sir.
-So…
-What?
Never mind.
I've never seen you speak so harshly
to a stranger.
What? You call that harsh?
You were being honest, speaking your mind.
Just like you are with us.
No filter whatsoever.
That's because…
That woman was talking nonsense!
The first person she's met
who felt like fate?
She never said "fate."
-She did.
-She didn't.
She said you were like a rubber glove.
Is that what you heard too?
Yes.
She must've misspoken.
"Fate" makes more sense in this context.
Why would she say "a rubber glove"?
I guess that's true.
Yes.
Hey, Ho-rang.
Hello.
Good to see you.
Cute, right?
They're kissing gouramis.
Look.
They actually kiss.
You call that a kiss?
Nice try.
Huh? What did you say?
Oh, it's nothing.
-What about the battery?
-That's right!
Look at this.
This is a brand-new model
straight out of the US.
It's nothing like the artificial hearts
we've used before.
Since we're replacing the whole device,
we'll have to open your chest a bit more.
But you won't need another surgery
for a hundred years.
A hundred years? I'll be dead,
but the battery will still be going.
You won't have to worry
about replacing the battery again.
I promise.
Tomorrow will be the last surgery
I ever perform on you.
After this surgery,
I'm going to start preparing
to take over TS Group.
I'm in your hands, Professor.
Your surgery's early tomorrow,
so get a good night's sleep.
-Cheers.
I heard Hanlim Advertising Company
landed the TS Resort ad.
Wow, classic Hanlim.
Seems like the company's really taken off
since Seol-hee became director.
That's all Seol-hee. She's that capable.
Seol-hee.
How's the wine?
This is Romanée-Conti--
Sweetie!
Pour me another.
More.
Hey, wine is supposed to be--
As much as you love me!
That's strange.
Is this how little Si-hun loves me?
There's barely any left, you prick.
Oh, I see.
It's not Si-hun's love that's lacking.
Turns out you're just small.
You can't even fill a wine glass.
Damn it. Hey!
Si-hun.
If you want to impress women,
spend a little more.
And put a little more heart into it.
Don't be so cheap.
Come on, Seol-hee. I'll give you a ride.
I'll head out first.
Seol-hee!
Get in.
I don't ride with drunk drivers.
Goodbye, Do-yoon.
I'll just call a designated driver.
What?
Gonna praise me?
Yeah?
I did well back there, right?
Don't be so mean to Si-hun.
He's hitting on my sweet Seol-hee
without knowing his place.
You do that too.
Don't say that. It hurts.
You think some cook's on the same level
as the director of TS Hotel?
Do-yoon.
To me, a loser who cooks and a loser
who rents out rooms are the same.
Shouldn't you at least be TS Group's heir
to talk about someone's place?
Hey, Han Seol-hee.
Baek Ho-rang
has no plans to marry you.
You're not even on his radar.
Do-yoon, make sure you call a driver.
Don't become a public laughingstock again
over a DUI headline.
All right. If everyone's ready,
we'll begin the procedure.
Scalpel.
That stings!
I told you not to touch me
with your bare hands.
You should always wear gloves.
Huh?
What? Did the power go out?
What about the UPS?
There's a problem.
The emergency power isn't coming on.
Two, three minutes for the generator.
What now?
-Quick, turn the hand crank!
-Okay!
Nice and slow.
Ma'am, hold on.
Is surgery even possible in the dark?
Don't hospitals have backup power
during blackouts?
I'm a little scared right now.
I'm not going to die
during an appendectomy, am I?
Ms. Na, the emergency power is coming on.
I think the lights are coming back on
because of me.
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
I think the power's back because of me.
Cardiac arrest!
Another mil of epi!
Vitals are stable.
Blood pressure's good. 120 over 80.
Okay.
Reduce the flow.
Closing the chest.
Huh?
What's going on?
Why is he here again?
Excuse me.
Wow, this is so strange.
Why doesn't my electricity affect him?
If this guy really is my rubber glove,
does that mean I can touch him
and even date him?
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang